Hello credential. I am extremely pleased
to bring to all of you another episode
of our own crew view with some of our
best leaders across our group. I am
privileged and thrilled first to
introduce the party alongside me and
then we will get on to some very
exciting discussions. On my immediate
right is Alvin uh one of our great
leaders and you hear more from him. Uh
next to him is Park. People call him K
though we all know Kamchi Ming. Millie
is next from Indonesia. Hi. Um, amazing
talent. Mrati herself is building a team
uh which is again extremely solid. Last
but not the least, Nicole from uh from
Hong Kong again an amazing leader and
very very successful entrepreneur uh in
her own regard. Um I am pretty excited
uh to be doing this discussion and I
hope you will learn uh quite a lot about
how very diverse set of people coming in
from very different backgrounds
have been able to make such successful
and inspiring businesses within
credential and let if I may start with
you uh first of all Paka I mean you have
been in this business for
>> 46 years
>> 46 years Right. And you have seen
changes.
>> Mhm.
>> Right. Whether it is regulation, whether
it is products, whether it is consumer
trends, competition, right?
>> Opening up of the economies and all of
that. As we are going through these
changes, how do you see this is
impacting our business park? How you
inspire your team to be ready for the
change that is happening so constantly?
Uh when I start in this business uh
mainly most of people want to try to
come into this business and maybe earn
some fast money. But after we joining
this industry for sometimes then our
mindset totally change because we feel
that this is much more important is this
is a missionary business. In actual fact
we are actually helping to many many
people. After we genuinely want to serve
our customers and everything then they
really slow solely change their mind
their mindset really the business can
maybe change our family uh uh these uh
financially and also the customer all
our customers financially as well. So
that means that what we are doing is to
help them financially independent and
also have a peace of mind in their
family. But the problem is is so easy
that we enter into comfort zone because
of the glory of success after sometime
because of success or money then we
don't listen and don't learn anymore
then because of that we stay in the
practice and never grow. couple of
things which which really resonate with
me and as a learning one is we do well
for ourselves by doing good to others
right that's the that's the core of the
business
>> that doesn't change with anything that
that is changing right
>> the second thing which I heard is that
don't get into your comfort zone
>> it's easy to get into your comfort zone
>> right
>> Nicole you are operating in one of the
most dynamic zones
>> in Asia Yeah. Right. Um Hong Kong, we
have fantastic local Hong Kong business,
right? But we are also seeing a lot of
business coming in from
>> Yes.
>> offshore businesses
>> in all of this and as you build your
team, right?
>> As you go for selecting new advisers to
to build your team and enhance your team
and make it bigger, what are you looking
for? What's your view of what's a
successful advisor in the future is
going to look like?
>> Okay, I think we are looking for the
advisor uh must have two core competence
of course must be the knowledge and the
sales. The first one is cognitive
empathy. The second one is digital
influency.
Cognitive empathy means uh its ability
to understand a custom special financial
ecosystem
uh such as their business, family
dynamics and the aspirations then
emotionally connect with why behind the
goals. The second one is um digital
fluency. Digital fluency is not about
how to using um a or tools. It's not
only about that um but more about
leveraging technology to enhance human
um connection. For example, we are
looking for the recruits who can curate
very special digital and customer
experience which is seamless,
personalized and uh provides value
between the al reviews,
>> cognitive empathy. Can you double click
on that and sort of share with us some
examples in the way you look out for
that empathy when you are talking to
prospective advisers. How do you come to
know that they are demonstrating that
cognitive empathy
>> because a good sales not will just sell
a product from the selling part but
always based on the buying point. What
does it mean? uh maybe our product have
many many you know the uh selling point
but maybe it's not match uh for the
customers the needs and wants. So we
should based on clients and needs and
wants this is just the basic um
capability the advisor master can use
the emotionally to convert that to we
hold the solutions. Yes
>> that's terrific. I I see what you're
saying as uh advisers need to
demonstrate a very good combination of
heart and mind.
>> Yeah.
>> Alvin coming to you man.
>> Yes. um newer generation,
>> Gen Z and you know even
>> beyond Gen Z, right?
>> They are thinking very differently
>> both as employees, potential employees
or as customers and they are the
workforce whom we have to also hire
>> right as we grow our business into the
into the next generations.
How have you and your team or how are
you looking towards that and what's your
pitch to them? What's your pitch to Gen
Z's and the younger generation to come
>> and join this very meaningful industry
as Bakam was talking about?
>> I guess Singapore is a market that very
high speed for changes.
>> So I I mean for the last 22 years I saw
it transform from insurance sales to now
talking about financial spending. So for
the people who joined the business last
time the mindset is about selling
insurance after that it became like I
want to be my uh own entrepreneur. I
want to set up my own business.
Currently people is talking about be a
professional. We are always comparing
our career together with like lawyer,
doctors and all these because the things
that we do is really very different
right now. And therefore when come to
the financial consultants we we give
them a a mindset that you are not here
to do sales you are here to become a
professional because of the changes in
the market and the whole industry
because it's getting more
globalizations. So you realize that our
consultant the things that they need to
learn is getting more and more
sophisticated. So we learn things beyond
our products. So youngster like this
they like to be seen as a profession. So
and we give them a mindset whereby
changes is constant and why this
industry been changing is just because
we've been expanding. Yeah. Our market
is getting bigger. We are looking at the
different countries. So with the kind of
the mindset that the young consultant
that they have, I'm not joining
insurance company to do sales but I'm
joining this company to become a
professional. Yeah. So that is a mindset
that they have and in the team itself we
have of course we have consultant from
the different background. So for the
senior who joined the business for long
we always tell them that you are here to
inspire the next generations. So it's
your responsibility
to bring the generations to become you.
So for the new generation who join the
business, we also told them that you are
here to inspire the senior. The rookies
come in, they become the IC for like
events and some like more leisure kind
of activities. They like the ownership.
They like to be the one who take charge.
So that's how we work hand in hand. So
everyone have the different role to
play. It's it's great Alvin and know I
think um in our business it's very few
businesses
where four different successful leaders
like them in different countries can
have the empowerment of building teams
based on their own principles. But the
powerful thing which you said is that
how do we include them right
>> uh become a part of becoming a
professional rather than a seller.
>> I also like the fact that you're saying
we bring them in and we ask them to do
something which they are good at and
what they like. Willie moving to you. I
know you are extremely passionate about
the purpose of this business. You have
been in MDRT for
>> 16 years. 16 years and you started doing
MDRT in Indonesia when the concept of
MDRT itself wasn't that big not only
credential but as as an industry that
really talks about your commitment and
your purpose and looking at this
business beyond just the financials of
it how do you look at what's our key
deep purpose in this business and any
story personal stories that you would
like to share about that
>> yeah Indonesia is actually a developing
country. So probably like uh Malaysia a
long time before uh when people want to
join insurance industry for the sake of
money for the sake of the uh better
compensation and at that time people
also uh not having insurance and they
just want to buy insurance and then they
buy insurance from their friends their
neighbor their relatives and that's it
but now uh the situation is changing
while uh people are not more more aware
about the insurance and this is I think
the best time for Indonesia to create
the awareness that actually insurance is
not only just a protection but actually
it really protect your dream. They have
dreams and they are having uh dream for
their children and uh the insurance is
the product that can assist them along
the way. I joined insurance industry in
2004. In 2017 when I was 42 years old I
was diagnosed for a cancer. I can see by
myself how insurance benefit to my life
and of course at that time I have
husband I have uh my children who were
at that time 14 years old and 11 years
old I was also feel so so worried about
my life about my future I have to focus
on my uh medical treatment but the most
important things is with the insurance
that I'm having the hospitalization was
paid and also the critical illness also
was paid and it can can cover like uh
five years annual income that is the
rule of thumb that I educate my clients
that at least you have five years annual
income for your coverage and when I
received the claim from predential and
it really give me peace of mind and with
that amount of money that I can continue
and can I can perform well and thanks I
recover from my cancer. So I look at
that insurance product is not only a
protection but it we are having a
purpose and this is what I talk to my
client that you need to have insurance
for your future for your family as well.
>> That's that's terrific and it's it is
moving to hear your personal story of
having gone through and thank you for
sharing it with all of the all of us.
It's so magical that what you spoke what
Pakam talked about doing well for others
and therefore good happens to us. your
theory about cognitive empathy. If we
compare all of that, Alvin, you
mentioned about bringing in new people
and making them professional
>> rather than sellers, right? If we bring
all of this together, I can at least see
the kind of magic and powerful vision
that you are building in your teams. One
last question to each one of you. What's
one advice that you would like to give
to youngsters or people who are keen to
join this industry and even thousands of
good leaders that we have young leaders
>> don't limit and don't judge yourself
before you really give yourself a best
try because uh you never know how much
you can really achieve in this career.
What I want to say is that uh this
business in that fact the first thing is
it's too easy for us to enter into
comfort zone. So that's why what I want
to uh share with others is uh always
remember one thing. Use your beginner's
heart pursue our eternal journey. This
is very important
>> for those who wants to join the
insurance industry. I can say that this
industry is the most beautiful industry
because it gives us three eye income,
independent and impact.
>> This is a place I like to work and this
is a place I can be a nice person and
this is a place I can grow up. So why
not join us? Don't hesitate just join
us. Yeah,
>> these are all leaders who have come from
very different backgrounds and have been
extremely successful in building
businesses here. This was quite
inspiring and and definitely insightful
and thank you very much for joining me
uh in this episode of Proveview.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Thank you.